<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Advanced Analytics for Web</title>
    <link>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/advanced-analytics-web-accelerator/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Advanced Analytics for Web</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 17:24:05 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/advanced-analytics-web-accelerator/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Add Enrichments</title>
      <link>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/advanced-analytics-web-accelerator/en/enrich/enrich_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/advanced-analytics-web-accelerator/en/enrich/enrich_1/</guid>
      <description>Snowplow offers a large number of enrichments that can be used to enhance your event data. An enrichment either updates or populates fields of the atomic event or adds a self-describing context to derived_contexts.
For this project, we&amp;rsquo;ll enable the IAB, UA parser and YAUAA enrichments in your console:
The IAB enrichment requires purchase (included with Snowplow BDP)
IAB Use the IAB/ABC International Spiders and Bots List to determine whether an event was produced by a user or a robot/spider based on its’ IP address and user agent.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Load sample data (optional)</title>
      <link>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/advanced-analytics-web-accelerator/en/modelling/modeling_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/advanced-analytics-web-accelerator/en/modelling/modeling_0/</guid>
      <description>Skip to the next step if you have a Snowplow Pipline and data loaded in your warehouse.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t have a Snowplow pipeline, you can load sample_events.csv to your warehouse to run the data model.
Attachments sample_events.csv (35 MB) We will be loading the data using the Snowflake Web Interface. For more details please check out the official Snowflake documentation.
Step 1: Create the ATOMIC schema If the ATOMIC schema doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist, create it in your target database.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Setup</title>
      <link>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/advanced-analytics-web-accelerator/en/tracking/tracking_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/advanced-analytics-web-accelerator/en/tracking/tracking_1/</guid>
      <description>There are a number of options to implement Snowplow tracking in your website or single page application.
Select the required pathway to implement tracking on your project.
JS React Angular Step 1: Download sp.js Add the sp.js file to your project directory. The latest version can be found here.
Step 2: Add JS snippet Add the below snippet to all of the pages you would like to track. Make sure to update the link to the sp.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Streamlit</title>
      <link>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/advanced-analytics-web-accelerator/en/visualisation/visualisation_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/advanced-analytics-web-accelerator/en/visualisation/visualisation_1/</guid>
      <description>Streamlit uses Python to build shareable dashboards without the need for front-end development experience.
Download the streamlit-visualisation project template and copy the unzipped folder to your project directory to get started.
Attachments streamlit-visualisation.zip (28 KB) Step 1: Install Requirements Run the command below to install the project requirements and run the virtual environment
pipenv install pipenv shell Step 2: Setup Database Connection Open secrets.toml and add your Snowflake account and database details.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Install Snowplow dbt Package</title>
      <link>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/advanced-analytics-web-accelerator/en/modelling/modeling_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/advanced-analytics-web-accelerator/en/modelling/modeling_1/</guid>
      <description>Step 1: Add snowplow-web package Add the snowplow-web package to your packages.yml file. The latest version can be found here
packages: - package: snowplow/snowplow_web version: 0.9.1 Step 2: Install the package Install the package by running:
dbt deps </description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Tracking Events</title>
      <link>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/advanced-analytics-web-accelerator/en/tracking/tracking_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/advanced-analytics-web-accelerator/en/tracking/tracking_2/</guid>
      <description>The trackers create data on user actions at a specific point in time. For example:
Loading a web page Clicking a link Submitting a form A number of tracking events are available out of the box. These include, but aren&amp;rsquo;t limited to:
Page views Heartbeats (Page Pings) Link clicks HTML form actions Pageviews and Page Pings In this section, we will implement page views and page pings.
JS React Angular Step 1: Enable Activity Tracking First we will enable activity tracking to collect page ping events.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Adding Context</title>
      <link>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/advanced-analytics-web-accelerator/en/tracking/tracking_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/advanced-analytics-web-accelerator/en/tracking/tracking_3/</guid>
      <description>Whilst the tracking set up provides event data on user actions at a specific point in time, context describes the setting in which an event takes place. To describe the context of an event, we need to define and capture individual entities. For example:
The user performing an action The web page the action occured on A product that has been interacted with Together, these entities make up the context of an event.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Setup dbt Package</title>
      <link>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/advanced-analytics-web-accelerator/en/modelling/modeling_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/advanced-analytics-web-accelerator/en/modelling/modeling_2/</guid>
      <description>At this stage you should either:
Have tracking and enrichment setup, as well as:
Data in the ATOMIC.EVENTS table Enabled IAB, UA parser and YAUAA enrichments or
Loaded sample_events.csv to your warehouse, as well as:
Data in the ATOMIC.SAMPLE_EVENTS table Step 1: Setup Variables The snowplow_web dbt package comes with a list of variables specified with a default value that you may need to overwrite in your own dbt project&amp;rsquo;s dbt_project.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Testing</title>
      <link>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/advanced-analytics-web-accelerator/en/tracking/tracking_4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/advanced-analytics-web-accelerator/en/tracking/tracking_4/</guid>
      <description>The Snowplow Chrome Extension can be used to ensure the event was emitted correctly but the browser extension does not check that the event was processed correctly.
Step 1: Installation Install the Snowplow Chrome Extension, you may need to restart your browser. Step 2: Check your data Open up devtools (F12) and navigate to the Snowplow extension. You should see a list of Pageview and Page Ping events start to form as you interact with your site.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Testing the output</title>
      <link>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/advanced-analytics-web-accelerator/en/modelling/modeling_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/advanced-analytics-web-accelerator/en/modelling/modeling_3/</guid>
      <description>Data should now be loaded into your warehouse. In this section we will take a closer look at the output to mitigate data issues and get familiar with the derived tables.
Step 1: Check the output schemas Head to the SQL editor of your choice (e.g.: Snowflake Web UI) to check the model&amp;rsquo;s output. You should be able to see three new schemas created:
[your_custom_schema]_scratch: drop and recompute models that aid the incremental run [your_custom_schema]_derived: main output models you can use in your downstream models and reporting [your_custom_schema]_manifest: tables that help the integrity and core incremental logic of the model Step 2: Run dbt test Run our recommended selector specified tests to identify potential issues with the data:</description>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
