<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Next steps on Advanced Analytics for Web</title><link>https://snowplow.github.io/advanced-analytics-web-accelerator/next_steps/</link><description>Recent content in Next steps on Advanced Analytics for Web</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://snowplow.github.io/advanced-analytics-web-accelerator/next_steps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Model your pipeline data</title><link>https://snowplow.github.io/advanced-analytics-web-accelerator/next_steps/next_steps_1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://snowplow.github.io/advanced-analytics-web-accelerator/next_steps/next_steps_1/</guid><description>At this stage you should:
Have tracking and enrichment set-up Have some data in the ATOMIC.EVENTS table Enabled IAB, UA parser and YAUAA enrichments Have a working dbt project with the web model configurations for the sample data Step 1: Complete refresh of your Snowplow web package (Optional) If you would like to use your current dbt environment that you set-up during modelling the sample data you might want to start from scratch.</description></item><item><title>Visualise your pipeline data</title><link>https://snowplow.github.io/advanced-analytics-web-accelerator/next_steps/next_steps_2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://snowplow.github.io/advanced-analytics-web-accelerator/next_steps/next_steps_2/</guid><description>Assuming you have already set-up your Streamlit project all you have to do is change the schema variable within the secrets.toml file under the streamlit-project-web folder and rerun the dashboard.
# .streamlit/secrets.toml [snowflake] ... schema = &amp;#34;YOUR_NEW_DERIVED_SCHEMA&amp;#34; Run the command below to run the streamlit locally:
streamlit run Dashboard.py</description></item><item><title>Custom models</title><link>https://snowplow.github.io/advanced-analytics-web-accelerator/next_steps/next_steps_3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://snowplow.github.io/advanced-analytics-web-accelerator/next_steps/next_steps_3/</guid><description>If you have got to this stage, congratulations! You are ready to take action and use your Snowplow generated data to help your business grow.
As a next step you might want to check out our detailed guide on how to create custom models to adjust the snowplow-web data model to your own needs if the out-of-the box solution does not fully fit your needs.</description></item></channel></rss>